canfinhomes.com 2016-04-11

# Privacy Policy

                                      Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy is for the website - www.canfinhomes.com and served by Can Fin
Homes Ltd. (in short ‘CFHL’) and governs the privacy of its users, who choose to use it.
The policy sets out the different areas, where user privacy is concerned and outlines the
obligations & requirements of the users, the website and website owner.
The Website
This website and its owners take a proactive approach to user privacy and ensure the
necessary steps are taken to protect the privacy of its users throughout their visiting
experience. This website complies with all laws applicable in India and requirements for
user privacy.
Collection of Information
In the course of using the website or availing the products and services vide online
forms, CFHL may become privy to the personal information of its customers, including
the information which is of confidential & sensitive in nature.
CFHL is committed to protect the privacy of its customers and has taken all necessary
reasonable measures to protect the confidentiality of its customer information and its
transmission through World Wide Web and it shall not be held liable for disclosure of
confidential information when in accordance with this policy, with the customers.
Web Browser Cookies
Unlike any other sites, small bits of data called ‘cookies’ stored on user’s computers is
used to stimulate a continuous connection. ‘Cookies’, helps to store information about
your preferences and passwords allow you to move to different pages of our secure site
without having to re-enter your password information. Any information collected is
stored in secure databases protected via a variety of access controls and is treated as
confidential information by us.
Use & Disclosure of Personal & Financial Information
CFHL will protect our customer’s personal information against unauthorised use,
dissemination or publication in the same manner in which CFHL would protect its
confidential information of like nature. However, under certain conditions CFHL may
share this information.
CFHL may use the personal information to improve our services to the customers and to
keep the customers updated about its new products or other information that may be of
interest to the customers.
CFHL may share information in the course of normal business operations, such as
providing services which the customer has subscribed and any activity related to these
services such as collection of fee/dues. It may become necessary for CFHL to disclose
your personal information to its service provider & agents in the course of normal
business operations for the above referred purpose. CFHL will endeavour to take all
reasonable steps to ensure that the confidentiality of the customer’s information is
maintained by imposing strict confidentiality standards on all the third parties to whom it
discloses such information.

CFHL may be required to disclose customer’s personal and financial information to the
statutory authorities in connection with any legal process that may be initiated by such
authorities in accordance with applicable laws.
CFHL may also share customer’s information to provide him/her with superior services
and a range of offers. This information may be used to advise the customer about the
products, services and other marketing materials, which according to CFHL, may be of
interest to such customer.
The Customer authorises CFHL to exchange, share, part with all information related to
the details and transaction history of him/her to its Affiliates regulatory
authorities/banks/financial institutions/ credit bureaus/agencies/participation in any
telecommunication or electronic clearing network as may be required by law, customary
practice, credit reporting, statistical analysis and credit scoring, verification or risk
management and shall not hold CFHL liable for use or disclosure of this information.
Exclusions from Privacy Policy
Other websites that the customer/user may access via our website may have different
privacy policies and access to such web sites will not be subject to this privacy policy.
The customers/users are recommended to read the privacy statement of each such
website to find out how they protect their personal information.
Amendments
Due to changes in legislation or enhancements to functionality and content on the
website, CFHL may make changes to privacy policy (without being obliged to do so) and
would reflect those changes in this privacy policy statement. Hence Customers/Users
are requested to go through the privacy policy statement on a regular basis.
Non-Binding
Please note that this privacy policy does not create any contractual or other legal rights
in or on behalf of any party, nor is it intended to do so.
Prohibitions/Restrictions
While using this Site, Customer/User agrees not to, by any means (including hacking,
cracking or defacing any portion of the Site) indulge in illegal or unauthorized activities
including the following:
    Restrict or inhibit any authorized user from using this Site.
    Use the Site for unlawful purposes.
    Harvest or collect information about Site users without their express consent.
    "Frame" or "mirror" any part of the Site without our prior authorization.
    Engage in spamming or flooding.
    Transmit any software or other materials that contain any virus, time bomb, or other
     harmful or disruptive component.
   Remove any copyright, trademark or other proprietary rights notices contained in
     the Site.
   Use any device, application or process to retrieve, index, "data mine" or in any way
     reproduce or circumvent the navigational structure or presentation of the Site.
   Permit or help anyone without access to the Site to use the Site through your
     username and password or otherwise.
In case the Customers/Users feel that their privacy has been compromised, you can
contact on grievance.redressal@canfinhomes.com.
Governing Laws
Any dispute arising out of the content, information, material, etc., provided on this
website or violation of the Trademark and Copyright rights of CFHL shall be governed by
the laws prevalent in India.
